What the heck what the what the what the what the what the what the what the heck my god, you're rich
I'm gonna sing a fiddler on the roof. So
Here I'm gonna play the Secky awakens song real quick. Okay. Go ahead. Oh my god. You're so rich. Bye
Love you. I love you more
The cards laid out for show
Star shine is so bright
Watch the secrets unfold
There's magic in
That was a smooth transition.
I think my phone was behind a little bit.
It wasn't that delightful.
I just took to my own saliva.
I felt like a goldfish in the fucking air.
We're all back, we're all back.
How do I change the picture so I have some,
see the my little J's vibrating?
How do I make it?
Stop it, you guys.
Let's get restarted.
Yeah, let's get restarted.
Oh no, what is that?
Is that me?
that's my dad right there oh my god that's my dad no is not your dad what's
with the white with the white area that was my god oh my god rest in peace
my dad looks a lot more native american than that god rest my dad's soul
Oh, there you go. Okay. I forgive you Hebrew him or for doing that.
You asked me for it. That's the only reason why I did it. I did. Now I'm asking for it. Was I asking
for it? Did I ask you nice? No, I was asking for it. Did I ask you twice? Hey, Trisha Licious,
Trisha Licious is here. Come say hi if you want to see Trisha Licious. Trisha Licious.
I have seen Trisha in her bikini and she's a fucking dime
Oh, yeah, what happened to the last stream? Did I miss the last game? Okay? Yeah, I got donated
It so I don't mess up that
He just did a cartwheel. He did a car and he was naked
No, I don't like I don't think so because it makes you look like you're probably
You look like that guy on what's a billy day old lady
You look the grandma up on the psycho movie
Page was good
That's good guys. Hey, okay. No, I look fine. Okay. I look good. I'm trying to look like
Who are you convincing?
It's myself. I need to convince myself. The cat. The cat. Yeah. The North, the North fooled the North. The North ran away
I
Scared the fucking cat
The cat caught a mouse the other day and I go we'll pick it up and I just see it
He goes oh, I heard a crunch and I'm like wait what I was like guys. I wanted to see the guts
They eat their brains like
It's cuz it's a cyclop in for them, yeah, yeah, and leave the pause and tell behind
You're like, thank you for all the gifts that are dead on my deck. I think it's like the equivalent of a dick pic
You're like, thanks the gesture was nice, but I'm gonna throw it in the garbage
I throw the trash and I think good kitty kitty
Yeah
Wait, what's page list by the conjuring house
That butt looks like the conjuring house
My butt's the great that's the tiniest butt I ever seen
Come on guys, we got it sick. We got it sick.
I told you mine. It's like I have a badig butt. It's not big. It's not small. It's not round. It's not flat. It's kind of just there
She just made this
I just have a butt to have one to have to hammer it is Hebrew hammer since time in prison
What do you think Hebrew hammer if I was like, you know the shallow would you say?
It's perfect. If I got hit on the head with your Hebrew hammer, would I save money better?
Greatest part is you people are so fucking done that I'm not Jewish like that's the best part
You know, do you know what a Hebrew hammer is?
It's a rifle. It's a foul. It's a 308 battle rifle. It's like the right arm
Do you know it? Do you know what the right arm of the free world is? Have you ever heard of that? Okay, here we go
Also a firearm. Yeah. I don't like it. I'm just letting you know like that's what I do
You know what? I'm actually not as done as I look and I was just making a joke because it's like page page is cool
Hey, like um
I
Keep the elephant is I know Kate the turtle not keep the elephant
No, I just think it's funny that people are like constantly
Chewbashing me and it's like it's so funny because I'm actually like more German than I am anything
But I'm actually Native American, you know what I think of Hebrew hammer. I think of a giant Jewish dick. Oh my god
You're usually very small, thank you
No, I think, I mean, I love that. See, this is, this is, this is productive conversation.
Yes, very productive. I haven't seen one. I've never been with one. I'm actually a Jewish,
and I've never slept with a Jewish man, okay?
Well, but I'm I'm Native American. I'm nervous over the native. Okay. Let's dance
Mr.. Hi, I walk the I'm not a teepee creeper
Okay
Rizor, what do you like it Riz? Rizor. I like Rizor. He's my buddy Rizor's dope
Devil eyes up by Vana. What's up? Trishalicious. Who else we got in here?
We've got the human race's biggest fan.
Double eyes.
Samantha.
Oh.
Yeah.
We had everyone here everyone all the all the class all the other
Classics, there's there's there's some fucking normies. We're more of the normies. I think right some goats in here
Well, they all make the same stupid
And you guys remember babe
Tracy, yeah
What is up? It's been a while. Hi my eggs. What's going on devil?
All the friends. Hey, what's up psychies friends? What is that? Familiars?
Juice's show is not on the bottom left. That is who is this person that is uh,
Who is that? That's my, that's in my, my blinds.
I'm the peeping tall
Wait a second, I'd be a peepin' mom, I would be a peepin' mom.
It's most hot.
It's hot.
Come on, Tracy.
Get up here.
Get up here, Tracy, girl.
Come on, Tracy.
Tracy, it's been a while.
I'd love to see your gorgeous hair.
Tracy.
Tracy's cool as hell.
I know, right?
I've known Tracy for a very long time.
We go way back.
We've got some good motherfuckers in these communities, but it's also got some bad ones too
Psy, so Ivana that's asking on the right hand side. That's not Kate the turtle they're asking about
No, Kate the turtle she's not here, but she was here. Yeah, I missed her. She's cool. She's cool. I like Kate. I like um
A lot of cool people like Barry, you know, Alexandra's cool
The man or the woman
We did that last year you're like are you still grounded for 30 days? Yes
So weird
I'm such a rebel that would be me like wanting to put like put my beak in every other day
Like did you really mean 30 days and I'd be like hitting my beak on the glass or night. God. Are you here when I got?
Or I got
There we go. Already asleep.
Here comes God coming up.
I'm not going to do it because I just realized I might be showing my butt like not a lady.
Oh, thank you. Why is it so hard?
This is a ghost panel
Those are cute
I'm in the back
I
Don't want to
I did some really bad
Yeah, you did do something really bad
Nor
I see Rudy. Hey Rudy come here. Rudy come here. Rudy, I saw Rudy. Alright, I'll see you all later. Sorry for saying that
I didn't mean to say stupid fuck.
They'll stay blessed.
Fortnight
There's Raven.
There's your girl, Jamie.
Say hi, baby.
Hello.
It's a good girl.
Please, baby.
Come here, sitting in your chair.
Come on.
Hey, Missy.
Yeah, how cute.
Oh, I want to move that, actually.
I think well at least I got to see her. Thank you. You're welcome. He heard me. Raven, did you see here Jamie? Yep. Yep. Immediately. If I could send you like a duplicate of Raven.
Who has a wrench?
What about it?
I don't know what's happening why is there really any strain look at you guys I'm gonna
make a jury out of this when it dries and I'm resonating.
But until then like what are you doing?
Oh
Fuck man, I was gaudy. Yeah
I didn't think it was me
Is it me
Do we go black or white or color
Look what I just killed
It's not me. Listen, I'll kill you right now. It's a ghost panel. Yeah, that's a ghost panel, bitch.
Oh, we're painting painting with page
What are we painting
Oh, look at that. Oh my god. Oh my god. She's smearing it. She's smearing it all over the place.
Well, that we have paintbrushes. Who needs them?
Well, I can't fucking golf. I gotta do something else. I like
Do you like shuttin the fuck up? Do you like shuttin the fuck up sometimes? That's his thing
Hey, pull me a card again
Are we doing all white?
You're restarting
Like an old trash canvas that I got for free and I was like I can do better
You kind of look like
Before you judge me on my appearance ghost I would like to see yours
No, I was just in your pain. You're always the 10 in my eyes
You know what goes fix the fucking mic man
All that fucking money can't have a good microphone I golf without shit. It's not even him and it's probably me
That's better now I can't hear you
Well, yeah, cuz my mic was shit. There we go. I
Do this because I like to I feel everything why not feel it right? It's a fucking paper. It feels cool
How do you wash it off? So it's acrylic paint
Oh, it's water-based, okay
Yeah
Hey ghost, I'm sorry I accused you falsely
Do I still look a dumb dumb or is my mic better? No, you still sound like a dumb dumb. It was me by the way
It wasn't you and what we know
We know that we all knew that why don't we start with red?
Look at that
Yeah, bloody up
Okay, should we do a swipe a dip a pour? What do you want to do? I think a swipe would be nice
Well, that would be nice, but I think if you want to be like it's a ghost panel
I think a little bit of blue when there would be no no no no. No, we'll start with red a
Little bit of white or a little bit of blue or a little bit of light. We're starting with red
No, no, no, no, no, no too late. Oh
God
You know what?
Okay
These are all pre-mixed with pouring mediums
Goose is using a dildo
Oh shit you dabbed. I fucking dabbed
Alright, this is gonna be beautiful. That's right. All right. It's nice
Patriotic the American flag. It looks like yeah against my country. Oh, you need to add is like a maple leaf
Let's do
No, this is Raven I can't pick her
She'll be bluevin
Do you want green in there? Do you want gold in there? We've got lots of colors
Is that better
It's the maple
It's the maple syrup in my veins or what?
In the trees.
The trees are kitchening and clapping for you.
Oh, look at all that gold.
You call it that, right?
This is like a Christmas tree now.
You're a Christmas tree.
I am.
Yeah, if you're a holiday.
What?
So where's Rachel?
She's somewhere gawking.
Come see, come see, baa-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-
Oh, there it is.
This is a page original, everyone.
Well, they're all original.
This is page original.
It's supposed to be ready.
Wait a second.
Can you hear me? I
Get a quick I got a quick question. Yep, so I got so was it was it frozen? I got couldn't come on
Well, who's making that squeaky noise? Let's go. Okay, so I have an iPad, right?
And it's on my big screen TV on my TV. I can see that pretty lady page
cooking right or baking
But I'm not doing either, but that's a cool. That's beautiful. That's beautiful
But like all my eye pitch is just a picture a little black in my picture
No, it's a 2025.
No, I mean it has an old image.
Yeah, so what's wrong?
What do I do? Anything?
I'm just going to reset it.
I don't know how. Okay, I'll just look at the TV and look.
I don't know what to do.
I did. I turned the whole thing off and came back on.
No, and you still did it?
Yeah, I'm just a judge.
Well, it's not even near done, you guys.
What are you going to do? Bake it?
Like, in my easy paint oven or what?
Get the hairdryer. I'm not gonna do a desk blow
Somebody say blow
Wait, do you say blow jobs or do you say
Oh, you're a bug now, goat, God.
I almost called you good, God.
I know, I just killed one of these.
I just killed one of these, guys.
I'm like, what the fuck do you do?
It's called an earwig.
Ooh.
Yeah, it was a earwig.
You can have those in British Columbia,
and you find them in your tin slots,
and we also have the really polioli potato bugs, too.
What are they do they just roll up in a ball like a little bitch, but the other one's
You can play marbles with those
You know what I have all over my balcony
Stinky bugs
What is the deal those are nasty
They look all innocent but they say if you come up and squish them they puff out a little stinky smell.
Oh, you blame it on them, huh?
You blame it on them when you fucking light up the room?
Yeah, blame it on them.
It's me with a lot of glue.
It's me with glue.
You farted the other day, I heard you.
That was a stinky bug.
You farted on film.
Can you guys hear me better or not?
You didn't see nothing.
That wasn't me. That was Sabrina.
That was Sabrina, man.
I was there. I was there. I was there. I was there. I was there. I was there. I was there. I was there. I was there. I was there. I was there. I was there. I was there. I was there. I was there. I was there. I was there. I was there. I was there. I was there. I was there. I was there. I was there. I was there. I was there. I was there. I was there. I was there. I was there. I was there. I was there. I was there. I was there. I was there. I was there. I was there. I was there. I was there. I was there. I was there. I was there. I was there. I was there. I was there. I was there. I was there. I was there. I was there. I was there. I was there. I was there. I was there. I was there. I was there. I was there. I was there
What would you like to do?
Would you like me to do it?
I'm not going to do it.
If you're going to do it, you should probably...
Snap of my fingers, sir.
I can do it.
Do it and see what happens.
Oh, no.
It's going to happen to you.
Snap of my fingers.
You don't fuck with God, pal.
Because I'm back. I'm back as writer die now. That's right girl
You could talk about this
You have no idea what the fuck you're talking about, man
Ghost panel tonight, let's fucking run one if I sent my finger who's gonna be gone
What are you gonna do? And if you don't like if you don't like it talk to the side
Talk to what I want to put that in my kitchen
What me pronounce it way you are in breakers
Call the sign you fucking dumb dumb wrinkles
Okay, we need a swipe color now. We don't you know why fuck you and your painting
I don't even black black black something swipe
Do you have like a new one hundred dollars? How about yellow? I already paid
Give me one minute
See how it works. Whoa, what happened? We took care of that
Oh snap food. That's right
You and your monopoly money God is God
That's right. Oh God you're making my dick hard if I had one God is God God is God
Johnny could buy and sell you
I'm such a simp for you, man. I hate it
No, no, Joanie can buy and sell them
Yeah, right. I know people. And I'm chosen, by the way. I didn't ask for it. I came out
that way sideways. I didn't ask for it. It's not my fault. Take it up with you.
You're blessed. You're blessed. Thank you very much.
so i've decided to go with like a dark black like a black cherry to go over or i'm gonna
white like a pastel or a dark vote pastel or dark go dark i love it i love when you go dark
colors can suck my non-existent dick i know i thought you were gonna say ass
i have i have a whole ass did you say ass next time yeah
Well, it's not like I can do it yet, I'll just stay ass, whatever you- whatever you-
Thank you, please.
People from an undisclosed stage
Natalie being backfussed by hothead
Mods prayin' Lord, not again
Where is he at?
Baby hold your ground
When the chaos hums
Like a feedback sound
We don't know who's sane
Who's banned or blessed
But the vibe's unholy
And always possessed
Scotty causin' from the bone
Bragg, he just dropped a...
I thought it was Johnny and Jesus or at least some sleep.
Mm-mm, it's all so true.
Ghost is connected.
You connected.
Canada's driving time down.
Randall's still typing.
Wait, DeVita just banned me.
Laughter, static, cat me out.
Me out.
In on-stream noise.
Get low, we're going low.
I'm gonna crash the fuck out. I'll give a lot of money. Not that I was the bomb here
I'm gonna crash the fuck out a lot of dumbasses to be here. We should be thankful. I
Didn't do nothing. I'm just sitting here innocent. Well, you didn't do nothing, but be retarded. I mean, it's not
Yeah
What up? No, I didn't I never want that now. Don't call them up
The burden of proof is gonna be on me. You just texted me and said ghost told me to put your backstage
Yeah, fuck it put everybody backstage fucking. I'll say it right now in front of everybody. I paid for this put everybody backstage
What do you want? What do you want? Oh?
It's just being you know, you wanna dance
I can do where the fuck
Shut the fuck up. I want you back. No, I want to dance
The bullshit around this fucking these panels you pay a little money you get a little respect, you know what I'm saying
What happened to page of the painting?
He can come back and like literally 10 seconds though
Well, I'm getting tired of being disrespectful on here. This is ghost panel, right psych I
Sponsored the panel. Obviously, I know it's your channel, but I sponsored it shut a band again
God eat. Don't speak unless you're spoken to you sir. Oh
And that can prove it cuz I want a debate you guys are sitting here like talking about finger painting
No, no, no, I didn't pay a hundred fucking something dollars for fucking finger painting
I'm here. I'm here to fucking have open open discussions. Oh, I'll fucking leave
Vanda money for an open. What do you want to talk about? I'll fucking leave
Jay you you you are you you have a little bit of the tism. I'm not gonna leave. I swear fucking leave
Then fucking leave nobody gives a fuck
What do you give nobody
I'll fucking leave leave. No, no, really. I'll leave keep it up. Oh
Keep it up. Keep it up. Keep it up. Hey, you know what keep it up once you pay more. Yeah
I might leave right now. Why do you not like so much? I'll leave I'll leave I guarantee I'm a fucking burning you up
But go ahead one over the last time when I left you had a shitty ghost over. That's what happened
All right, dumbass
Unraveled
Go ahead and leave though. All right, go ahead
You've been uninvited sir. No, no, I'm not gonna leave. Go ahead. Bye
What area you're gonna stay now? Yeah, go ahead. You're all of a sudden all of a sudden magically you're just gonna stay
I'll be quiet. I'll be quiet. So you don't know what the fuck you're talking about. I thought you're just leaving
Please
We're trying everything we can you'll make a part of your ass. What are you trying everything you can when are you trying everything?
Okay, that's a good
Ghost panel you're he paid for this so we have to play
Jay how much do you charge 150 or something yeah, I can get some head
Yeah, why you what what the fuck do you mean? That's the same fucking. That's the same logic
I
God we're talking
How to drive motherfuckers we're besties so here. What are you gonna do Paige? What are you gonna look like?
It doesn't mean you know what?
And I don't give a fuck to find you
Indians and like I mean we can make a debate about that, but you already lost that
This could be you
This this could be
Another word say another word against me
Fuck you, Gotti
Yeah, what's gonna happen? What's good? What's gonna fucking happen? You're gonna set
Be kind
Now fuck the pain. We don't want the pain. We don't want the pain.
No, no, no. I want to see the pain. I want to see the pain.
Let's go, panel! Paid a lot of money for this. At least let me fucking.
Can we not have fun?
I want to see the pain. The paining was cool.
I don't want no fucking pain. Fuck the pain.
Let's go, panel. It's spooky season.
Well, it's been a month.
Yo, it's takeover season.
Hey, look at Raven.
I'll take over.
And you know what?
Tonight, we're going to have a...
Everyone's invited tomorrow.
That's not even.
We're going to have a good night.
Oh, tomorrow?
Okay.
Good.
Tomorrow, I won't be here.
You said they're telling me to take over
because everybody's sleeping.
You know, fuck all that.
Goddy's being a bitch right now.
Good.
I'm not going to be.
I'm going to make sure I'm not here.
What time is it gonna happen because I don't want to be here when it happens?
Well, all right, that's cool. Well, that's fine. You paint with that finger
Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my
god. Oh my god. Oh my god.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha
I actually don't get it, do you explain to me?
I'll leave I'll leave I'll leave I'm out you don't have to kick you know it'd be really
cool painting with blood I'm serious about this.
Think about it. Think how cool that would look on a canvas. A nice maroon color.
You get that deep rich blood right in the canvas.
I feel like this, but kind of like this, but from this.
No, but real blood because you'll know it's real blood.
That's what I mean. I know.
Are you going to be like, hey girls, I'm trying to like, I'm not doing nothing. I'm trying to like paint.
Uh, do you mind if I paint? I would have said no problem page. Go ahead. Never
She was painting before you took over
She's halfway through halfway through the painting you you paid 50
What does it say that one card does it say dumb dumb
Yeah, I can't believe that.
It's the sweetest morning here.
Well, it's 1.30 there.
Nobody wants to hear your fucking pain.
You little fuck.
I want her to make cupcakes too.
Don't tell anyone!
Cupcake. That's what they're good. You know is a guy that paints with shit and he makes a lot of money
People buy that shit
Guess what's gonna happen tomorrow, it's gonna be a ghost being
Can I just paint my face way and bring all my actual ghost friends or what?
Would you just say I'm sorry
I
How could you be that cute and paint?
I'm complimenting the lady
She's so pretty and she's
Well, yeah, because the bitch is gonna do something for sanity purpose. I'm just
Paint that body paint that body. Sorry. Did I say that? Sorry
You're fucking retarded. What's this now? What is this?
Is that flammable
It's all it's a pain condition. Are we all gonna do a shot this is a 70
Got you room now
Sorry ghost you ruined it man. I actually like you. I actually want it. I'm sorry dude. I'm sorry
Sorry, bro
We had a we had a make-up such
I just did
All right, I'll let you back up page. Yep
Would you like to apologize? I'm sorry, sir
Okay, Jay. Well, I I'm not gonna ask Jay. Jay. Would you like to?
No
Jay you know what you know what I agree with you got he's not a good friend at all
Who said that somebody say that
Card if you say nice things and stop tell me what to do
There's no card pulling going on right now
They're all dumbasses what else back up, where's Alex that
God is a bitch
We're you going Johnny
What do you want me to do I got you may take my top off I mean you're not you're not giving me nothing
I can't
See the gamer
This is what they do
But it's too much. I can't take what your argument don't fuck
Those the people
Ghost, damn
Fucked interior card. You heard a ghost. He's a ghost. He's a fortnight ghost god
I don't know what I'm your work right there. Trust me. Oh, I would destroy you in fortnight. So far
You know what I'll use I'll use beef boss. I'll use beef boss and I'll destroy you
Guess what's gonna happen tomorrow night? Well, I'll see the unveiling
Anybody else want to run one
All these people are fucking
That's nice
Hey girls don't fight you're making the cat fight
No, no, you're in your head
Like a purple
You know, you're younger you're never supposed to have the green lifesaver, you know what I mean
But like then you kind of want it because it's the bad one
You know what colors I don't like is the pastels.
Oh, I don't like pastels either
Are you iPhone are you at Android?
The 17 yet or what are you on? No, I'm still on the old 12. No, you aren't you cheap ass
I gotta have a pro max I get a 15
Okay, well, I'm ready. I'm getting ready to upgrade to the 17, but I don't know yeah
I'm gonna wait till the 18 actually. Well, that's a year away. Yeah, well, I can wait
Okay, well Trump will be gone. Oh, did I say that? Oh, sorry. He won't be actually he will be double
I'm psychic. I'm sorry. I hate to tell you something. Yeah, give me some numbers then. It's
Maybe by Christmas maybe by March. No, give me some numbers like lottery numbers
I don't know. It's just something's gonna happen. It's coming. Yeah, everybody's saying
27 to 13 and 12 27 32 13 12
You know, let me write this down
27 13 32 and 12
and six
Six and 12. Yep 13. Okay. I got it
I'll show you get 20% of whatever I went. Oh, I don't even need nothing. I'm just happy to help
Wait, wait, wait, I think I fucked it up. I wrote 13 twice. What were the numbers again? Oh
27 13
12 6 and there is one more what the fuck did I just say?
There was one more shit somebody rewind the fucking stream
Ready, I don't know if you can see but you see it, right? Oh
Yeah, that's cool
Look at the yellows how they fucking pull through I like that I look what she's doing
She's she's smearing it all into one color talented. She's married. Somebody be lucky to have her exactly. I was married
Yeah, we're done with that, right? Yeah, at least you tried it once
I think it becomes like a marriage then becomes a business. You know what I'm saying
So you were just what happened? Oh ghost just watch this watch this. Okay?
Where is this is a ghost panel by the way
Oh, guess what? It's been
Now we're not going to watch shit. I'm asking you questions
I need any
Fuck, you want to read after me?
Would you like to read a card for that? I paid more money
It's my panel
Pool card
Are those real boobies?
Yeah, of course they are
They look real boobies
For you. Oh, she's doing a pride if you put fake one
What she's doing easy baking
I'm creating heat because when you apply heat to any paint
So what it's gonna do is gonna react to anything and then the heat helps bring cells to
And the Float Troll helps with an attitude as Creed's lacing.
Kick everybody, I want a 1v1.
You know what, the real classics use this kind of technique.
Don't you have like painting music behind you?
Like Van Gogh and that.
Kick everybody, I want a 1v1.
Did you watch, did you anybody watch Severance, the show?
No, I never watched that show.
Oh, that was good.
It's over now.
Is that ketchup?
Ketchup.
She should use ketchup.
I had to be cool.
Ketchup.
We're going to paint only using the food items mustard and ketchup mustard and ketchup. That'd be fun mustard and ketchup
Yeah, it makes a little male
He's like mustard and ketchup and bologna liquor and horse
Bologna has a
It's a la
Look at you good. What is what are you on tonight? Sorry
Well, she's can't be sober. Can't you be like this sober? Of course
But i'm not sane
You're not sane. Okay
I keep wanting her to be really really cool
I want this to be food
If you just bent over and put your shirt right on the canvas, right? Yeah, and and yeah
Like the t-shirt would be the whole painting
Yes, yes, yeah, just put it right on top of the canvas
Paint in my braid paint in her brain
Is he mad well tomorrow's tomorrow's this panel he said
Goes is he really mad? Does he want his money back? Oh, no, he's not he doesn't get money back
What does he want from us? Oh there you are come on buddy. What do you want?
I think I just want don't kick them, but put them backstage. I think me and you real quick
You'll be the worst thing you ever do in your life
Go
Well, she didn't give a hundred dollars. She didn't get $50. So what?
Fucking reading dude
Tomorrow night is ghost night. No, I don't want the reading though. I give a lot of money not to hear it
a lot of money. I'm so sick of hearing about money. I know. That's rude, Ghost. I pay a lot of money not for your treatment.
He keeps talking about it. Can you imagine if you're like a hooker and he paid you?
How much have you done? Oh my God. He wouldn't let you go. Well, he kept demanding more and more. Always.
He'd go deeper, farther.
I give another 50 and I'll go back to the right me. That's it. Oh, they're long
Are you gonna fuck me over then? Oh my god, what do you want you want your
No, don't be a bitch in room. Don't be a bitch. Hey, ghost. What do you have to eat in the house anything good? Yeah
What are we eating
I love bacon
No, she's not going to make bacon with her but her pain. I thought she's gonna put that on the painting. Oh my god. Oh my god
I don't know
Bacon or we put it in the skillet. We're gonna go hog wild
Oh
Spit that on the page on the up on the canvas. Yeah
A little DNA on that. Oh, she's drinking the pain
Oh, it's what soda. Well, don't fucking text me either. I'll fucking know
I'm not texting you
I love when he gets mad. I like the better when we're fighting
Goddy because that way I did that won't be so
We can go back and we can do it again
And I feel powerful and you know what you know what Joanie I lied. It was me. I knew it was
Was it really it was don't do that to me. Yeah easy it is
That was you wasn't it. It was the whole time. What's the name of the show? I don't even know
It wasn't me it wasn't me promise. Yeah, that's where I swear on page. I swear on page a hundred pages boobies all the time
Look at her. She's so cute. She'll make me go gay
Where was it? Where was it anyway? Pines? Yeah. I never go to pines. I've never been there.
I thought you went once. Oh, I don't know. I went once but I didn't say anything. I know.
He's a weirdo now. He's only got mean trolls on there now. He's a weirdo now. Oh my god.
From what I've seen, he looks like he's always been one. Oh my god. The night when he...
Yeah, I don't know the lore. I don't know the lore. It seems like buddy wants to switch over and just like stop doing everything
Yeah, which is which is cool cuz you know whatever I know you try to make him like you know
I saw it when he was trying to be funny after yeah, I guess I don't but I did have a good time the other night
What it would really tell him the jokes and stuff. It was really felt good. He is funny. Yeah, he's great
even if he's uh, even if he's not shitting on somebody he's still doing it
So yeah, whatever that's my kind of stuff
Did you like him when he sat behind like the fake presidential desk and all that? That was funny too. Yeah, I get that's my kind
But then he was saying stuff that it wasn't true. I guess so that's weird
It doesn't matter what he says
See that thing Joanie, I come from that same kind of culture where yeah, we'll say everything and anything about somebody and then the next day
It's like a new clean slate, you know
But some people are all ready to get a lawyer and say I'm exactly some people ready to kill you and right, right, right, right?
That's their problem. I'm right. I gotta learn I'm learning
We're here to have fun not to have wars and fuck yeah each other. Yeah
Crash out and all that shit
What do you think's gonna happen tomorrow or today?
Yeah, I don't give a shit fucking he put more terror son. What do you think about the more terrorists?
I don't know what he did. What do you think about him blowing up all those boats? You like that or no good?
I love it. I love it. You know if they're all guilty. Oh, hey, man, they're on speed boats running drugs
So right, right be skiing and I don't like his bathing suit bottom boom. Yeah, they can go. I don't give a shit
Something's gotta be done, Johnny
To a point what we're doing doesn't work. So whatever whatever he doesn't for it for the most part. I don't know
At least he gives a fuck
You need somebody who cares I
Don't know I'd like to be a fly on the wall on that Putin phone call, you know what I'm saying
Now trust me Johnny, whatever he said to Putin. It's for you know easy
It's for our benefit. Trust me
Mm-hmm are his our benefit. You don't you don't fuck around
No, but he lines his pockets to come on guy a guy who's worth seven billion dollar. You're worried about him lining his pockets
Are you kidding me?
No, let's not fight about it. Okay. We're not fighting about it
But look at all the people that really line their pockets that sold us out over the years 40 years of Pelosi and all these other losers up there
That have been taking money from us
That's all right. All right. Let's meet the middle
I'm sorry cuz like I'm not gonna be able to convey there'd be something we have no chance you have no chance
No chance right you're one of them and my family's like that too. So don't worry about it. I just don't go to holidays
you lose out
They got the tv blaring with the news that channel and this and that you don't have to listen. He's like, fuck george
What's his name floyd? Oh, oh the cats. You don't have to listen to that stuff. I try not to but what am I gonna do?
I lost my whole family to it. So
Oh, that's crazy. I know it is crazy. You go over there. You have a good time. You say, haha
I'm not listening to you. I know you're right. You're right
You're right, baby. You're right. They still love you. You come with me. You come come come to come come see me
And then you'll have to come then you'll leave in the middle of the whole thing
The whole they always do the chair spins
We got two ghosts. Oh no. Oh my god double vision wait
double vision
And I'm gonna give you guys 10 more seconds. I'm
Is that
Thank you, you know, thank you and page you and that painting in those boobies bye
you. Page is the captain now.
Hey, you're the captain now. I
love your little cabin hat too.
Johnny, thanks for being on the
show. I love you, Johnny. Johnny
is great. She is really, really
great. Hi, what's wrong, Tricks?
It's ghost panel, dumb fuck.
I don't think there was one
Look at how beautiful that looks
Bag it
Is this the final step
It's a final step. This is almost I'm almost completely. I'm turned into a panelist almost. Oh, you're welcome psyche by the way
Oh, thank you. Thank you God. Thank you. I gave you a lot of money, but now it's the final step
Well ghost I love you
Would you like a little piece? Yeah, I would love a little thing very agrees with me
Very fresh. Yeah, you know Barry knows you that you look tricks. I say hi. Can we say hi tricks? Trixie
Look at his face
He's like, oh my god, I'm being fucking raked. Oh, come on
He's fine. Hey
Ghost you okay
Oh shit
He's depressed cuz are you cool somebody pissed them off like
One-card page. Can you can't pull me one card? No
Okay
And one then one for ghosts because ghosts I think ghosts need some guidance in his life, what about you?
Ghosts are you there?
Yeah
No, I can do it. Just give me a sec. No problem. Hey, you know guys
I just want to say I love you guys so much and it's like I'm sorry if I'm not the best friend all all times
But I will try to be better friends. Okay
Well, that's like that's a good start psych you just be you all right
We'll decide yeah, we'll decide whether you're gonna decide I really I don't think I'm like
No, you should say no, that's not up for us to decide fuck. That's the first step of accepting self
But you know what? But then people are mad at me and they must be mad at me for a reason. Oh, well
People are mad for whatever
But I love everybody I really do love even like my worst enemy
I have well I can find like a little bit of love for like that's like we have to accept you with your flaws and all
That's it. That's how it works
I'm flawed. I'm a flawed mother. We know
Very flawed and look at like I'm like
not the not a good panel hose I'm not a good I don't good enough you're good
enough how about that thank you when you wake up in the morning you look in the
mirror you say I'm good enough that's it don't get you through the day don't
worry fellow you're good enough but you know what you guys make me better you
guys make me better and I love you see how that works
Every time you say money we do a shot. Yeah, I have a little bit of beer
I was just on tiktok like hitting on a bunch of guys and
I throw them a few roses and they're receptive and so
Heaven right now. I'm in heaven. I got my
Hot guys
Oh, do you want to give me my money back? I mean, no
There's no
I mean
Suckies boys gonna run it with them. Yeah, we're on it good
hey hey you know what I guarantee I'm gonna fuck you up you want to debate
You can't it's good panel. What are you saying? What for you don't have to run your own fucking panel?
Shuttle band again
Dude, I gave you a lot of money. You should actually run your panel. Oh my god
I got a fucking money money money money
Damn money
Shut the fuck up. We're talking money money money money. Okay, cool. Shut the fuck up. We're talking
Like yeah, you honestly at this point do you kind of art? I mean I have to agree kind of piece of shit, man
Who you talking to
Can't even treat me with enough respect man. I don't want your fucking money
I gave you some money fucking money
I don't need his money page
I'm fucking sitting on a mountain of gold bitch
Maybe fuck yeah, we're supposed to have a ghost night tomorrow. It was supposed to be like you yeah, you can have a ghost night
It's gonna be gone
I'm tired of this shit my company a fucking party. I
Ain't coming to fucking party either
Company of funeral
But you're on a shirt
It's like you that's fucked up there's respect to me
All this money I gave you all this money I gave you
This respect all this money I gave you
I'm supposed to be in bed about an hour ago, but I'm waiting to see this painting
Fuck it's ghost panel
Fantastic it's like those balls from fantastic
Yeah, I'm sorry. You're not
going to pick it up at all.
This room. Don't know if
anybody else gets that kind of
money, but I did. I'm still
talking about money. Hey, that's
what goes there, but you paid a
ton of money and none of us
did. Yeah, I gave her a lot more
money than you guys did. What's
You keep what's your point lay down?
Yeah, I think my point is a guy I did give a lot more money in you
Okay
What's your argument?
You stressed me out. That's why you don't know what the fuck you're talking about
Shut the fuck up. Good guy. What's your argument? That's what you want to say to me right now
Yeah, I do I want I already want to hear my argument
My argument is that when I walk into a place to eat and they have Pepsi products. I walk out. You know why?
Because I don't drink that
free
It's not me. I'm sorry. He's not being a bitch
Who
No, you want to have the argument
You're talking about I think you sound stupid. I mean I'll go
I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I
I'm so happy did I have been working on
These are the ones you made
The star the other star
That's death I don't like that one like she's been
Anyway, I'm sorry short. That's not this is about I've only got like this many done because it's fucking some mad hours
Putting that shit. Those are good. Okay, so that's like five cards. I have plenty to go
So how many are in the major arcana 14?
Yes, there's what there's 48 interdex, okay
So who are we doing first are we gonna there's like a bit of an energetic battle right now?
Um, and it's between
I'm here. I'm here like you wanted to die. Yeah, thank you. There he is
I was just trying to get you rolled up because I know you've been waiting. I was just fucking around. I'm gonna do your first
Okay, you go
Yeah, yeah, okay, let's do it. Let's go then
Let's start with let's go pick gold or red
Ghost
Go
Ship it goes. Oh, you're not the one big gold goes. I hope you're watching this big gold
Yeah, but no, I'm not even gonna fuck with him like that. Like oh, he left. He left. Yeah, do psyche
Okay, you don't get it. You don't get a choice. I'm just gonna start you're gonna put gold
Okay
Okay, so first of all
Okay, this is gonna get a little a little deep psych
So are you you're you're definitely and you know, I haven't been around like I haven't been here for a while
So it's not like I would know personally, but you know energetically
I'm I'm like I feel anxious in my own
Like I feel uncomfortable in my own skin and it's not because of how I want to feel about myself but because of how others
Kind of over time have chiseled my brain into thinking that way. It's like I you feel you feel so
Alone, but at the same time like you could feel alone in a in a room crowded with people like a sardine can
You don't feel understood. You don't feel heard
You don't feel you don't feel noticed and you feel like no matter what you do you're coming across in ways that
You're like I can't win it's off putting no matter what I do
I'm just trying to be myself you try to do what you think people want you to do and then it's like but then you're like
But then I'm not being true to myself. It's a whole inner it what I want to call it like an intergalactic battle. I
Don't know. There's like there's a whole in
Your insides need some recognition and you need to be felt, but you have to be the person to start with that in order to start that chain reaction. Does that make sense?
Yeah.
Because as soon as you're secure and you're confident in everything that you do, I don't give a fuck what is it? Making a sandwich or fucking making a... It doesn't matter if you're on here or everything that you do, you have to put your utmost...
self into so that you're truest self because I think that there's just been a disconnect with that and
So it's vulnerable and it's easy. Does that make sense? Yes
All right, so it's like a carcass
And there's hyenas and shit.
Okay, yeah, vultures, vultures in the parking lot.
But you know, I feel like obviously,
I don't know if many of you pay attention
to astrology or anything,
and I'm not trying to be like that girl,
but I'm kind of that fucking girl.
Like just even just feeling it
and being a part of it myself and like at the real,
I'm a human in this fucking world
and I'm connected to the stars no matter what,
whether it's in a soul tie or in a physical level,
like three D or five D doesn't matter.
So,
It will affect you whatever planet is in certain houses that make up yourselves of you, right?
So it depends on what like direction it's spinning
There's been a lot of astrological significance that will affect us
Especially lately and when it's back to back to back to back like that. No wonder we fucking lose ourselves
It's not like it's just you guys by yourselves. It's not just like well my fucking medium. I know I'm struggling too
There's a reason I have not been on YouTube, right?
And if I'm not at my best self to assist or help you guys
or provide that my purpose or my goal on my channel,
then I'm not going to do it.
It's simple, right?
Because you deserve the best version of me and so do I,
and so does everyone else in my life, right?
Including my pets.
And it goes for everybody.
So that being said,
I also feel like you're not getting along with one of your siblings more so than usual and I feel like you need to talk to
Another sibling about it. I don't know why I'm hearing that and I feel like maybe there's something going on with like
I know that you and your mom are pretty close,
but I feel like there's just been a disconnect.
The more that you disconnect or further,
you disconnect from oneself, this goes for everybody.
The more that everyone else around you
feels it energetically and reacts to it
in the way that they're just naturally going to, right?
And so it's hard to be so self-aware, but so stuck.
That's what I'm feeling.
Okay.
Like why can't I I can help other people and I get great advice that I'm a you know
But I can't give it to myself and I feel like that's
Exactly, okay, so I'll pull one of these ones for you or however many come out
Are you thinking about changing your fucking hair color or something you want to like are you trying to do you thinking about looking into like a
Look or what the wig? I like a blonde hair
I mean aside from the wig I feel like you're you want to like you like like like ice highlights or some shit
Like are you trying to change?
My hair is kind of naturally highlighted a little bit, but yeah, that'd be cool. I used to do highlights
Okay, so
And by the way, Paige, I love you.
Thank you for being here tonight.
You're a star.
I love you too.
You deserve love.
All of you deserve love.
And I miss you guys a lot.
And I forget that I deserve love too.
And then I'm important as well.
You do.
Oh my gosh.
Everybody needs to remind themselves of that.
Also that you're a magic wand because you create
what you speak and you manifest your thoughts
and you project and attract what you feel.
Your vibe attracts your tribe.
If you're feeling off set,
you're going to attract the wrong company.
Okay, so we have gentle gardener, but it's came out in the reverse and in this deck
I very much do take the reversals because it is a so above so below kind of deck, okay?
so
in the upright
Ghost you're gonna be fine
I don't know if number two means anything to you psych, but the gentle gardener card all my reflections terrible. Sorry
It's kind of like Eastery harmonious
You know what I mean? It reminds me of that like that spring coming
It gives those vibes and like also being connected with oneself
You know being certain of the seeds that you've planted and that they're going to be fruitful and that they make up
Who you are and that you're not gonna fuck about none of that. I paid a lot more money than you're able to reading
I paid a whole
My reading so you can say what you want. I know that you like my readings and I know that you like me as a person
So yep. Yep. Just give me one sec and then I'll get to your reading because it's also important
It came out first, but you were fucking absent for your own panel. Okay
You know the dental gardener being in reverse like that for me is immediately clarifying
It's like my backs again. Like I'm just your your your
acting out of sorts and not of oneself because you feel like you're backs against the wall a lot,
like you're in a corner all the time. And so you're just on defense mode a lot, right? And or,
like, oh, well, I'm going to stoop to levels because that's, that's my only option of how I
feel and what I like feel in this time is best for me. But it's not. And because you're not going
to make decisions that are for your highest self when you're in that mode either, right? And that's
Okay.
My cards are clumping a lot too, which means like there's things that you're letting build up before taking care of them
And so it seems like it's a lot, but once you do it
It's like a 10-minute task and then you feel like the weight of the world is off of your shoulders
But because of all of the stress and like anxiety and all the shit you're going through on the inside
It's like impossible sometimes to
Not let those tasks build up. Does that make sense? I'm being busy as fuck
so yeah we have the gentle coming out again in a different deck but in the reverse as well
so and like I don't know if the
Number 57 means anything to you, but it's like penetrating a soft approach and like finding moderation in a subtle but depth deep
Influence and understanding and like so non-violence. So you're trying to find a way to
Settle all of your scores in a sense or like to kind of cross all your t's and dot all of your eyes and the most I guess
It's not in your most gentle manner not to yourself and not to others and so it's not solving anything, right?
It's just keeping you in that like kind of timid like hand shy
My owner used to beat me kind of mode, right rather than being like, oh, well
You know not all of them are that not all owners are that person in a sense is that makes I don't know
That's a weird fucking way to put it
we do have the turning point on the bottom of the deck and this is a really nice card because it
kind of gives you the options to come out of this and go whatever direction that you feel
needs like to come of you in your newest form, your new skin, right? So take advantage of this
I'm pretty look at and I am kind but don't take it for weakness because I will bite but don't be the snake and also don't be the bitch
Does that make sense? It's like find find you're in between and find that balance because that's where you came from originally
And that's who you are so okay that said I will pull the fucking
And it goes goes don't worry about it goes where I need I need this reading right now, okay?
So just give me a minute to get the reading
You also know how I roll if the cards come out and it needs to be said it's gonna be said like I don't even know how to do it
I really don't know how to fucking just do like a couple card reading
Whatever needs to be said is gonna be channeled through me and or these cards for your highest good and your best interest, right?
Yeah, so she's my friend it goes. I'm not gonna like
Kick off my friend. Okay. No, it's okay. Let me finish this reading and then you can kick me and then no one else gets reading either
Okay, so we look at this site. This is incredible
So we do have the strength card coming out in the upright and what does that lamb represent to you?
Gentle and kind and everything of that nature that has been in the reverse
This coming out means that you're eventually at like in a very
Within the next month at least you will be coming in coming in and you're already in the motion of this strength that you're going to
You're gonna start taming the beast with inside of you that everyone else has created plus of your own actions and everything that you've created
As well that causes turmoil that makes you less desirable you
does that make sense so it's like I'm overcome this and I'm gonna be I'm gonna find that balance
that's what we just talked about before the card came out right and so then we have the three of
cups coming out so you know it's time to celebrate after we've come to that realization it's time
to recognize and you know find that what do you call it unity right that like oneness in that whole
Self that you exude out to others and then your vibe attracts your tribe yet again
And then it feels like it's harmonious right this card really wants to come I tried and look at that the fool
So you're gonna just you know what you don't know what's at the bottom of that
But you kind of do at the same time because you're a psychic, right? So it's like I'm just gonna stop being frightened
I'm gonna let go fear. I'm gonna let go of all of the other shit that's involved and I'm just gonna say fuck everybody
I'm jumping off the high dive right and then you cannonball
And then you're like, you know what that was actually really worth it
I feel so much peace and she's holding an amethyst. So it's like just just the harmonious
Like mandala in the water all of it like all of that looks like it, you know, I'd go for a fucking dip
anyways
Let's tie it up. You're welcome. We've got we go right up that clear your fucking mind psych clear your mind
We've got that last quarter moon in Gemini and we've got full moon in Leo again. Go wild
So just be passionate about what you do and don't forget who you are and fuck everybody
You wear fucking American flags Speedos
Okay, there you go. I love your page. It is awesome. You know what? I love the page. It's like
the heart, the heart. I just see the big, big, big radio heart.
I'll let the girls so I can get a big dick. I've got a big heart.
This place is only better with page here
They will tell me that I'm a dumb ass
He's right
She knows her shit and also when you start your channel
I do have a website coming out and you're gonna be feature on the website always, okay?
You're awesome dude. You're awesome. I love you. I just don't want you to like, you know, I want you to have fun, but
People that are that are that are coming up and stuff like that
Because come on up I'll leave
I'll leave I'll leave it's okay. I'll leave
Why do you
I'll leave I'll leave I want him to be happy
It's a panel you paid a lot of money for this
It's okay
Just blow them site just blow them a few times it'll be fine
I love you ghost. Ghost, I really do love you and thank you. I appreciate you. Okay. I'm not appreciative. I'm really appreciative of you. I love you. Okay. I really do. I really love you.
You keep staking your life. I love you guys. Thank you for your reading. I love you guys. Thank you so much. I love you guys so much. Y'all the best. Ghost, come on up.
I don't hang around assholes and bitches. I don't hang around good people.
Now he's not gonna come up now. He's gonna play like hard again. So he has to be big now
So what do you leave that pain to drive for like a day?
and then I'm gonna do another one but I'm gonna do a diagonal swipe so I'm gonna
do like I'm gonna just line I'm gonna line certain colors in smaller like
little lines obviously though and then I'm gonna fucking just pull it down and
up so it's gonna be look like this and it's gonna I don't know I don't know
colors to do yet I haven't decided
I was going to do it on my panels or whatever, something different, because I'm like,
well, if I'm going to come back, I better bring something to the table, which she...
Yeah, people are going to love that.
You enjoy it.
It's called spiritual arts for a reason.
My stupid long-ass fucking handle has a purpose.
You know what I mean?
It's supposed to be like when it's expressing yourself spiritually and creatively and artistically, right?
Like and golfing motherfuckers. You see what these assholes do at these these museums they go there
They say that fighting for oil and then they throw tomato sauce on the painting. It's the next shit
Yeah, that's like that's like, you know paint and blood on first
I mean I get it like at the concept of it
But like each their own I suppose no they're ruining the the ancient painting like the old painting like the Mona Lisa
They want to go like oil
Do you know why because when they were little their mom didn't wipe their ass good
Go she's talking to you
Like your ass you heard
It's not my microphone, it's ghost
Oh shit
What's she do to the cat? She stepped on it
Those page
She goes off camera to do it
Ghost what are you eating?
I'm leaving fuck you ghost by page
Thank you so much
Psych yeah, I'll see you pal. You guys have a good one. It's ghost
Now don't leave now. No fuck that I want my money back at this point
Money banks, are you ready? I actually believe two hours ago. Now you're leaving you want me to go. I'm literally
Shut the fuck I wouldn't talk at all. It's not all about you by the way
Maddie believe it or not. It's not all about you. Well, apparently it's all about you because it's your panel
I didn't forget. Yeah. Well, it was supposed to be all about me
Well, it could be a dick and it will be all about you. We're gonna celebrate the joyous one
I can be a dick or why I mean I give a lot of money. Did I not?
So how much did you pay? I?
Don't know fucking at it up. I don't know. Hey, how much did he pay?
Yes, like added up how much I paid
You tell my total or just a night
I'm not gonna do that because I don't even have that right now. I'm not working but
It was just it was it was a concept it was just a
You're you I'm not going to laugh soon
Me me me once you pull me a fucking card, and you know what it's gonna say. It's gonna say traitor
You could say please and not be like I don't want to fucking come on page. I don't want one
Okay, well then I guess I'll go continue my joyous painting and I hope you
I want you to get a reason I want it goes to get a reason I and you better be polite
No, brother. We're gonna have to have a serious talk by the way. I need a reading night. We know how fun
Let it happen let it happen. I'll let one car
That's not fair. Fuck, it's my panel. I mean, we just, we have to, I'll let one card happen, alright.
Hey, what happened? Let it happen, Ghost. Let it happen.
Alright, can I get one card, please?
There you go.
Can I I already have it all planned out for you, so like
Like would you like an oracle or would you like a tarot or would you like a moonology?
There you go. What do you mean by Oracle though? What do you mean by that?
I actually don't even know what I'm gonna say.
They're not there. They're not there. They're not there. They're not tarot cards or oracle cards.
I think she means it. They'll have a message for you.
What oracle cards do you mean? Can I ask? Or am I just resorted?
Oracle. It's like a message for you. It's like a message.
Okay, so Tarot?
Oh, can I get it?
That base deck of cards. It's just illustrated in different ways, but like an oracle deck is an individual
Can I get one of them?
You just want one fucking card out of anywhere out of anywhere
One terrible card one oracle that's what I would I usually do. Thank you. Okay, so would you like the same deck go?
Would you like gold or red?
I would prefer gold. Okay. Wonderful. Let's do one. Do you know
Before I start with the cards
Yeah, so there is a level of like it's almost like it feels like
Heartburn, but like it's like it's like depression and in a certain area
It's like you swallow it down and it always comes back up and fizzles back up
Fucking card, please
Yeah
No room to talk tonight, dude
Your spirit guides tell me that you need to shut your fucking mouth
In the most polite way of course because they're kind
Yeah
Pick that part up. What does that card say? It says intention. How did I fuck up?
No, you didn't shut up. I think that's
I don't know if the number 22 means anything to you we have an owl sitting on an egg and it's got a
Dandy lion the ones that you blow like make a wish and blow it out into the into the universe
So whatever fucking just plants more weeds
But like logically you're planting a seed of intention and thought and it comes from a place that is not of
what you're
what projecting right now it's like you have an idea it's now going to be implemented and planted
as a seed and it will grow into some kind of abundance that I mean it could be monetary but
I feel like it's something that it will fulfill something within size you which is awesome because
I feel like it's been a long time since you felt really good about like like I mean I feel you know
Kind of just empty or debt, you know what I mean? It's no joy. It comes from anything at this point some sort of things do
Yes, I'm not saying you feel that
Can I ask you a question you felt empty in the past?
Like just just the stuff that you bring me joy or fill some sort of space that like
That as you're a person either like shut the fuck up
Ghost. What the fuck is wrong? Ghost.
Because
If you are you are reading they're reading to you and they're fucking
Okay
It's about respecting your spirit
I gave a lot more. I mean what I didn't ask for a reading my dad
Ghost just
Okay, how's that not nice? It's a ghost panel. How's that did she give you that much money like I did
I didn't ask for a fucking
Reading that I enjoyed and you
I mean my bad
okay i'm gonna end the panel but ghost we're gonna have a ghost
you're gonna end the panel again you're gonna run away from it again
i'm gonna play your song i'm gonna play your song and then i'll end the panel but ghost
well you're being a bitch don't run away from it
the fairway sun in her hair
maple leaves falling she don't seem to care
That's my Canadian
Three weeks like smaller than a month
I just love you
Every word she speaks
Feels like a golden age
No, no, no, don't act as if you didn't hear us
You know what I mean?
It's just like a wee eye
You fucked me over
Alexander's heart's gone all the way lost
And they're smiling those prairie days
Yeah, she's a sweetheart
A real life mate
That's my Canadian badass
My prairie page
I love you.
with that gentle grace you tied up with the coldest place.
Yeah, she's a good kid, she's about 20 years.
Love on stays, that's the legend.
She's gonna fuck me over, I can't even close to her feet.
There he goes.
I'll never fucking go over, I love you.
Ah, I forgot to say I'm a progressive individual.
I love you.
I've been doing this all the time.
I don't care for anything.
Why?
I'm not gonna lie, I can't hurt you.
That's a great place to go to.
I love you. I love you. I love you guys. I love you. I can't hurt you.
I'm not fucking going you fuck me over tonight you're gonna fuck me over tomorrow
Ghost you know much. I love you this much. You don't you don't love shit, but you don't love anything because
The Illuminati I am you talking to Illuminati. It's me. Okay. You know you did me
I am the Illuminati, okay
You understand?
I just shouldn't talk to you anymore.
I am the Illuminati.
So we shouldn't talk anymore.
That was it.
I swore you were Tony.
Yeah, I swore it was true.
You laughed it off, said psyche.
I'm just me, not that dude.
You're ready to crash out
when the moment feels right.
Top donated energy.
You light up the night.
Big brother in the chat.
Thank you ghost, I won't forget you. You make me laugh till my face turns blue
Jokes in the middle of the late night vibe
You're the spark in the storm
You're the wink in the crowd
Even when you're quiet
You're still so loud
Thank you, bro
Got that easy sway
If I had to choose
You'd be here every day
Thank you, bro
I won't forget you
In your quickfire mind
Not Tony, huh?
All right, Ghost, I believe you.
I believe you, baby.
Baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby.
Don't don't insult my page you poop
She's my poo bear. She's my like, you know, they ever see winning the poo and there's like piglet and winning the poo hugging
That's page of me. You're gonna don't pick on her
Don't pick on Gotti Gotti is like Christopher Robin
Okay
Say Christopher Robin
Me nice to me. Okay ghost
Ghost hey guys
You know what? I fucking love you, never forget that. I fucking love you, Jamie's Cowboys.
Jamie's Cowboys, if anything happens to me, you take care of Lenore, Trix, Lola, Rudy,
and if he comes back, Marbles, okay? Jamie's Cowboys gets to my cats, okay?
Nobody else. Okay, I'm saying it. I'm saying it live on my stream. It's not streaming like I'm a deleted
Jamie's Cowboys. You're gonna take care of my cats. I
Love you. Okay, I
Love you, Jamie. I
Love all you guys. Thanks for being here tonight. I
Gonna play the biscuit song and then I'm gonna I'm out. Okay
Yeah
came to the kitchen but forgot the recipe serving up crumbs while i feast on
legacy i'm the fire in the oven you just
all right it looks over guys don't rise because you came too quick
Peter's biscuits drying blend you know what it does
yeah just no hands clean you bring spice but you're bringing
We ain't finished yet.
Penal verse feast, we don't starve on lies.
Your plate got nothing but recated fries.
I'm the main course.
Truth served hot.
You're the snack that everyone already forgot.
Feed us biscuits, let's go to the stand.
Try to serve shade, but you played yourself.
Penal lights on, truth sharp like a knife.
Biscuits crumble, welcome to real life.
can't even describe.
but you're bringing regret
panel that receives me finished yet
you came to the kitchen but forgot the recipe
serving up crumbs while I feast on legacy
firing the oven you to smoke that won't stick
you don't don't rise cuz you can't do it
you can't just quit
dry your head
don't stab the dust in your hand
Everyone already